Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
Damn them, attacking our All-Stars...!
I would not do that...
Yes!
Kawamatsu!
Yeah, let's beat them to a pulp!
Hey, boys!
Don't even think about...
...giving them a hand...
...in their duels!
But Kingpin Hyogoro,
they're up against the All-Stars!
Whether friend or foe, you will keep
anyone and everyone from their fight!
See!
"Don't get in our way"
is written all over their faces!
All that's at the top
of the Red Line...
...is Mary Geoise, yup.
And you're not the kinda guy
to ask the gods for help, yup.
You're drunk
off your ass, huh, Pops?
You bet I am!
And those oh-so-great Celestial Dragons
live up there in Mary Geoise, yup.
No "gods" there.
Nah, I'm talking about
way, way back.
Long before Mary Geoise.
Heard there was this
"Land of the Gods" up there.
Land of the Gods"?
Saying stuff like that
ain't like you, Pops.
A long, long time ago,
upon the red wall...
Hey, Marco!
No sleeping on the job!
This is war!
I was just waiting
for you to help out.
Foolishness!
We are leaving!
Izo...
Believe in any gods?
You sound like Pops
when he was drunk!
Yo, bros!
Don't think for a sec
that you're gonna beat us!
Your attacks did squat to us!
Listen up, and listen good!
We are Kaido-san's protectors:
The Three Calamities!
They call us the All-Stars
because we're unbeatable!
What's wrong with you?
Well, after I put on my Raid Suit
for the third time, my body's felt off...
Just don't trip me up, got it?
Didn't say anything about
being under the weather...
Just feelin' weird.
Maybe it's your eyebrows?
I told you, it's my body.
First one you owe me.
Bridal Grabber!
Back down to zero.
Germa!
I heard all you kids of his're cyborgs!
Vinsmoke Judge...
Totally nuts, the madman!
That flaming leg
of yours a machine?
Too bad for you!
I'm a hundred percent human, unlike them!
Humans can't just
turn flames on like that, dumbass!
Unless you're a Lunarian, that is!
Oh, but we can!
Turn up the heat, that is!
My passion burns
hotter than any fire!
I can even cook up some
Sea Monster dishes with it,
you dumb dino!
I'm gonna show you
what cyborgs're really made of...
Somethin' even
Vegapunk can't recreate!
Eyes on me, black mummy!
The hell kinda blade is that?!
I get it now...
You're a killing machine...
Does one need
styles and forms in a fight?
Right...
You never called yourself a swordsman.
Have it your way.
Who knows, by the end of this
I might be tearing your throat out with my teeth.
Whatever it takes to win!
Kingpin Hyogoro.
When Hiyori-sama said
she would bequeath Enma upon him,
there was a reason
I could not stop her.
If indeed your blade is Shusui,
I ask that you would render it unto the Land of Wano.
I told you! That's mine!
You shall have a replacement!
A sword bequeathed to me
by my departed father...
It shall be yours...
Well, if you're trading one-for-one...
Yeah, I know why you couldn't.
He's a pirate from abroad, yet it's strange...
He is the spitting image of
the Daimyo of Ringo,
Shimotsuki Ushimaru,
in his prime.
Quite right!
Right down to his swordplay!
Ushimaru-sama was a descendant
of the God of the Blade, Shimotsuki Ryuma,
and a great swordsman.
Even the fact that he returned Shusui
to the Land of Wano feels like 'twas fate.
That, and Ryuma being a
one-eyed samurai himself...
Hit a wall, huh...
And you can't even take your Sulong form,
with no way for moonlight to reach you in here!
Bedtime for you, Day King!
M'II let off...
...that pile of rubble you call a country,
for keeping up the lie...
...that there was no samurai there!
Bring Raizo to me, dammit!
Or this time I'm loppin' it off!
I swear to God that I don't know
anyone named Raizo!
If there's anyone by that name here,
I'll slice my stomach open!
Oh, yeah?
In that case...!
Had we sold out Raizo then...
...our shame would
have been so unbearable...
...that we would not have
dared return here, to Wano!
Those your last words?
Lemme help you end it all...
by removing your head!
Ever since the day Oden-sama died...
we spent every
waking moment...
...preparing for this,
our final battle!
For two decades,
we asked ourselves:
"Are you still Oden-sama's...
"...samurai?!"
Y-You damned dirty dog!
That form!
How are you in Sulong form?!
A hole in the ceiling?!
You will not...
...Stain the name of
Kozuki Oden any longer!
Even if our
millennium-old city crumbled...
...we had to forge our way here,
to our ultimate battle!
No matter who among us dies,
we shall win this battle...
and the Dawn shall come
for the world!
The enemy just keeps
flooding out of the castle!
This is where our fates
shall be decided!
Piss off!
This is our castle!
Get outta our way,
damned samurai!
Leave, and nobody gets hurt!
Carrot, Wanda!
Master Nekomamushi!
Preciate you-gara all
savin' some for me.
I'll take it from here!
If it weren't fer Pedro,
Luffy 'n the others wouldn't be here!
This raid would be
one big flop!
Pedro, huh?
Looking to get revenge for that jaguar?!
What an awfully beautiful...
...full moon tonight!
Pedro!
Watch over us!
Hope yer enjoyin'
a drink or two, meow!
But fer you, Lick-Spittle...
This's the last moon...
...ye'll ever see!
Now that Oden is dead,
watching you idiot ghosts serve his brat is comical!
Shut your mouth!
Youth is nothing to laugh at!
Just as people like us
grew up to become Samurai,
others do the same!
Wano shall watch over Momonosuke-sama
as he transforms into a man!
And that is why we will not allow your ilk
to steal away our country!
Clone Technique!
To my ninja techniques,
I commit all my strength...
...So that I may lay waste
to enemies of the Kozuki!
Y-You gotta be kidding me!
W... W-W-What's
goin' on here?!
A-A-A dragon?!
Why's he here?!
Why S Kaido here?!
Can we even manage to fight him?!
Don't ask me to join in!
I am no morsel!
If you dare attempt to eat me,
I shall devour you first!
Restrain yourself!
It's dangerous over there, Straw Hat!
Stay away from him!
That you, Momo?
Indeed.
That's...
the runt we saw earlier?!
What the hell's going on?!
Nuuuuh?!
'Tis the work of my
Ripe-Ripe Technique!
At Momonosuke-sama's request,
he is now twenty-eight years of age!
You can do that?
Why the tears, though?
Because...!
Momonosuke-sama!
You are the spitting image of...!
All right!
Let's go, Momo...
We're gonna take back Wano!
Aye!
Huuuh?!
They all keeled over!
What's with you guys?!
Get a grip!
ND-Did you just...
...use Conqueror's Haki, croc?!
Caught me red-handed...
Miknew it, croc!
It's not your fault!
You just don't have the willpower to
stay conscious in my overwhelming presence!
I'm the guy that took out
two of the Flying Six!
Usohachi the Sibling Hunter!
The Flying Six!!
Two of them?!
Can't beat me? Join me!
I dun get what's goin' on,
but it's pretty amazin"
It's because Big Mom is fighting
on the same floor.
The rank-and-file here fell like dominoes
in the wake of her Conqueror's Haki.
Franky!
Any idea what happened to Luffy?
Not a damn clue...
But what Momo said earlier
is all that matters, yeah?
Luffy yet lives!
He speaks to me now!
Saying that he shall return!
Shinobu-chan's supposed to be with him,
but I can't reach her!
No news is good news!
Come on, what's that
supposed to mean?!
Come on down when you're done
doing what you gotta!
For some reason, the bad guys're
hitting the Performance Floor non-stop.
We could use a hand!
Huh? The Performance Floor?
Clik.
Yo, jerks!
Don't let 'em through!
Zoro and Sanji're fighting the All-Stars
on the Performance Floor!
Don't tell me what to do!
Aye-aye!
We're all equals in an alliance!
Ouch! Hooothothot!
I think I feel hot!
Though I'm already cremated!
Wait!
Who dares say I'm cremated?!
Robin-san is going to burn up!
Baron Corpse!
Are you all right?!
We can no longer
stay in the castle.
Would any of you know
how the war is faring?
No, it's just chaos everywhere...
But I did see the First Son of the Sea,
Jinbe, on the fourth floor!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
I reckon your captain is
still fighting Kaido, yes?
Wouldn't know...
I was wondering that myself.
That so...
The whole situation is a right mess.
We need to ferret out
where the key players are...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... clik.
Jinbe-san! Jinbe-san!
We have a problem!
The third floor will
soon be engulfed in fire!
You must descend while you can!
Fire?
That's definitely not good...
But who, exactly...
...is holding Kaido at bay
up there?
Narikabura Arrow!
Vajra Arrow!
You...
...can't be Oden!
You have always...
...been trying to kill me!
Yeah, that's right.
This ain't some
father-son quarrel.
If you really wanna call yourself "Oden,"
you better be ready for war!
I don't play games,
Yamato!
Is admiring someone...
...a sin?!
1...
...love Oden!
Away with you!
I will defend the Land of Wano!
Open Wano's borders!
Just brutal, man!
She's been like that
for a week now!
Don't back down now!
She's got Kaido-san's blood in her veins,
but she's still just a little kid!
Brute force her into stopping!
Brave words!
Then stop me,
if you can!
Stop fighting already!
Yamato-sama!
Wrong!
I am...
...Oden!
What just happened?
This your doing?
Yamato.
wwww
Wrong!
I am Oden!
I...
am Oden!
Answer me, Yamato!
Did you do this?
I do not know...
They all fell on their own.
Hey!
Unchain me, Father!
I am starving to death!
I see...
It's the Color of the Conqueror.
You show promise.
But if you're gonna keep
calling yourself Oden,
die!
Yamato!
Huh?
Whaaa!!
I'll give you a month...
How 'bout you
cool your head while you're here?
Wait! How can you just leave me
in a dark place like this?!
A-A month, sir?
The Ogre Princess may be tough,
but even she would die!
Besides, there are vicious
Wano samurai behind that door...
Just like that idiot over there...
You've got a month.
If any of you change your minds,
shout through the air hole in the ceiling.
If you decide you wanna be
one of my soldiers,
I'll let you out of there.
How many days have the
bunch of you been without food?
Hey!
Bring 'em some food!
But...
...just for one person.
Samurai gotta have
their swords, am I right?
Father!
I am the child of Kaido!
I know they bear me ill will!
If you leave swords for them,
they will kill me right away!
What're you talking about?
You're Oden, aren't you?
I may be Oden, but...
...I am also the son of Kaido,
Oden's murderer.
I know the Samurai
will absolutely loathe me!
Father wants us
to fight each other to the death!
And over a meal!
No, before that...
They will kill me!
Eat, please.
Uh?
Wha?!
No need to be so reserved!
Samurai do not feel hunger, you see.
A-Are you sure?
I...
I am very...
...hungry!
If none of you Samurai will eat,
then may I?!
Sure, go on.
Hell of a family you were born into...
Thank you!
Samurai are amazing!
Hard to believe you do not feel hunger!
Fank you aww...
Sammmurai...
I'll nebbr fuhget...
duh tashte ub dis meal!
Say...
Can I become a samurai
even though I feel hunger?
Hands in the air.
Y... Yes, sir!
Stay calm, now.
You're Kozuki Oden, right?
We heard you, after all.
We, too, love that man.
What?!
Are you people his friends?!
What is your name, Samurai?
Asking a defeated samurai his name?
Just call me So-and-So.
I want to read this journal...
...but there are a lot of
difficult characters...
Oden's logbook?!
"The world is made up of four seas
and one long strip of sea.
"Furthermore, the world is round,
much like a shiratama dango.
"It is truly perplexing!"
Ah... How long has it been?
About ten days?
I have no idea...
In here, nothing changes.
Yamato... Is your father really going to
let his child die?
At this rate, we may not be able to see the battle
that Oden said would take place in twenty years.
When that happens,
I will fight...
...alongside the Land of Wano...
And I will set out to sea...
...to become stronger
and stronger...
That's reassuring.
Then...
...by not allowing you to die here,
we shall be taking part
in the future war.
Hwuh?
Twenty years is...
...a little too long for us to wait.
Samurai!
If you do that, my father will...!
We would rather not
rot away like this!
We had no intention of
giving in to Kaido...
...from the very beginning!
We leave the
Land of Wano in your hands...
Kaido-sama!
They've shattered the Sacred Stone Door!
Don't let them leave here alive!
There are people who believe in me!
Who accept me!
Why do you want to
take away my freedom?!
And the freedom of
the Land of Wano?!
Life isn't a series of
simple questions and answers!
You damned whelp!
Thunder Bagua!
CONTINUED